<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Abstraction</title><link>/</link><description>Recent content on Abstraction</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><copyright>Abstraction is a computer science club at Calvin University that serves students interested in computer science.&lt;a href='http://eepurl.com/hpV8xz'>Mailing List&lt;/a></copyright><atom:link href="/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Game Development: Best Practices and How I Learned Them the Hard Way</title><link>/post/andrew-quist/</link><pubDate>Mon, 15 Mar 2021 15:37:59 -0400</pubDate><guid>/post/andrew-quist/</guid><description>SPEAKER: Andrew Quist
WHEN: March 19 at 6:30pm
LOCATION: ONLINE on Teams at https://bit.ly/3tnXiGJ
Details Calvin graduate and game developer Andrew Quist will be discussing his journey in game development and sharing some best practices.</description></item><item><title>Talk</title><link>/post/jason-html5-gaming/</link><pubDate>Wed, 09 Sep 2020 23:55:48 -0400</pubDate><guid>/post/jason-html5-gaming/</guid><description>Writing a Platformer in HTML5 and JavaScript by Jason Pruim
WHEN: February 20 at 3:00pm
LOCATION: ONLINE on Microsoft Teams at https://bit.ly/3ptVhGB
Details We&amp;rsquo;ll be discussing how a simple web game written in JavaScript and HTML5 is constructed, and provide a basic starting point for you to build your own.
Talk Resources https://github.com/Calvin-Abstraction/html5-games</description></item><item><title>Self Promotion</title><link>/post/hello_world/</link><pubDate>Mon, 09 Sep 2019 23:54:48 -0400</pubDate><guid>/post/hello_world/</guid><description>Are you a Calvin student with a project you would like to promote? Contact us if you think it&amp;rsquo;ll benefit others to share. We don&amp;rsquo;t guarantee to list you project, but if we do you&amp;rsquo;ll find it here.</description></item><item><title>2021 Opportunities Index</title><link>/year-2020-21/opportunities/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/year-2020-21/opportunities/</guid><description>&amp;lt;- Go to 2021s Main Page
Go to Resources Page -&amp;gt;
An index where you can learn about the opportunities and activities offered by Abstraction and the computer science department at Calvin.
Talks We are planning to have around 4-6 talks in the spring. To stay informed about upcoming talks, please subscribe to the Abstraction mailing list (this is not the GNU Mailman abstraction-news list).
Febuary 20, 2021 at 3:00pm - by Jason P.</description></item><item><title>2021 Resources Index</title><link>/year-2020-21/resources/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/year-2020-21/resources/</guid><description>&amp;lt;- Go to 2021s Main Page
Go to Oppertunities Page -&amp;gt;
An index where you can learn about the resources for C.S. at Calvin. Whether hardware or the people who make things work, we hope to make this index all-inclusive.
Physical Computers Please subscribe to the Abstraction mailing list (this is not the GNU Mailman abstraction-news list).
Links Email us links.
https://missing.csail.mit.edu/ The Missing Semester of Your CS Education GitHub Student Developer Pack Companies want your eyes!</description></item><item><title>About</title><link>/about/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/about/</guid><description>Our Mission We exist to serve the community of Calvin students interested in computer science.
We currently serve in a few ways.
We provide opportunities by hosting talks and promoting jobs and internships for the community to grow. We provide resources in the forms of people, hardware, software. We provide a platform to help grow the C.S. community at Calvin. Joining Abstraction Welcome! Other than subscribing to our emailing list, there are no formal membership procedures to join Abstraction.</description></item><item><title>Blog</title><link>/blog/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/blog/</guid><description/></item><item><title>Contact</title><link>/contact/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/contact/</guid><description>Contact us at abstraction@calvin.edu.
.
Sometimes you may have better luck with one of our personal emails:
Contact David at dar23 at students. calvin . edu Or Aaron at alb83 at students . &amp;hellip;. . edu</description></item><item><title>Leadership</title><link>/leadership/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/leadership/</guid><description>2020-21 Leadership Contact Us Here
David Reidsma (President) GitHub Aaron Brink (VP) GitHub Nathan Strain (VP) Jason Prium (Admin) GitHub Legacy Leadership Previous Abstraction leadership
Jesse Kuntz President and Vice President { working on it }</description></item></channel></rss>