<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Abstraction</title><link>/</link><description>Recent content on Abstraction</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><copyright>The Calvin Abstraction Club is an official student organization of Calvin College serving Calvin students interested in computer science.&lt;a href='http://eepurl.com/hpV8xz'>Mailing List&lt;/a></copyright><atom:link href="/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Self Promotion</title><link>/post/hello_world/</link><pubDate>Mon, 09 Sep 2019 23:54:48 -0400</pubDate><guid>/post/hello_world/</guid><description>Are you a Calvin student with a project you would like to promote? Contact us if you think it&amp;rsquo;ll benefit others to share. We don&amp;rsquo;t guarantee to list you project, but if we do you&amp;rsquo;ll find it here.</description></item><item><title>2021 Opportunities Index</title><link>/year-2020-21/opportunities/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/year-2020-21/opportunities/</guid><description>&amp;lt;- Go to 2021s Main Page
Go to Resources Page -&amp;gt;
An index where you can learn about the opportunities and activities offered by Abstraction and the computer science department at Calvin.
Talks We are planning to have around 4-6 talks in the spring. To stay informed about upcoming talks, please subscribe to the Abstraction mailing list (this is not the GNU Mailman abstraction-news list).
Jason [ more to come!</description></item><item><title>2021 Resources Index</title><link>/year-2020-21/resources/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/year-2020-21/resources/</guid><description>&amp;lt;- Go to 2021s Main Page
Go to Oppertunities Page -&amp;gt;
An index where you can learn about the resources for C.S. at Calvin. Whether hardware or the people who make things work, we hope to make this index all-inclusive.
Physical Computers Please subscribe to the Abstraction mailing list (this is not the GNU Mailman abstraction-news list).
Links https://missing.csail.mit.edu/ GitHub Student Developer Pack Companies want your eyes! Lots of free stuff.</description></item><item><title>About</title><link>/about/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/about/</guid><description>Updated Spring of 2021 Last modified: 2021-02-07 13:56:46 -0500 -0500 Our Mission We exist to serve the community of Calvin students interested in computer science.
We currently serve by:
providing opportunities: specifically talks, jobs/internships for the community to grow, providing resources: people, hardware, software, and providing and growing the C.S. community at Calvin. Joining Abstraction Welcome! Other than subscribing to our emailing list, there are no formal membership procedures to join the Abstraction Club.</description></item><item><title>Blog</title><link>/blog/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/blog/</guid><description/></item><item><title>Contact</title><link>/contact/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/contact/</guid><description>Contact us at abstraction@calvin.edu.
.
Sometimes you may have better luck with one of our personal emails:
Contact David at dar23 at students. calvin . edu Or Aaron at alb83 at students . &amp;hellip;. . edu</description></item><item><title>Leadership</title><link>/leadership/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/leadership/</guid><description>2020-21 Leadership Contact Us Here
David Reidsma (President) GitHub Aaron Brink (VP) GitHub Nathan Strain (VP) Jason Prium (Admin) GitHub Legacy Leadership Previous Abstraction leadership
~ give us some time ~</description></item></channel></rss>